Run Steam++.exe and everything will be installed. All the instruction code will be showed on-screen.

DO NOT RUN the .bat FILE ALONE.
DO NOT RUN the .bat FILE ALONE.
DO NOT RUN the .bat FILE ALONE.

This app runs hardware level syscom commands that are injected in the bat file. The only visible code
is the echoes which are the commands themselves. 


Features
--------
◘ Everything run as one program(the modules) instead of like multiple ones thus the entire proccess of steam 
  runs faster because of that.(it's like instead having 20 chrome processes for each tab you have only 1 )

◘ Improves the overlay performance by rendering all the modules(friends panel, community hub....)
  at once instead of each other. [ Tested with PUBG ]

