◘◘ How to Install
-----------------
Run Steam++.exe and everything will be installed. All the instruction code will be showed on-screen.

◘◘ How to Uninstall
-------------------
Run the .bat file alone then delete the file called 3


Description
-----------
This app runs hardware level syscom commands that are injected in the bat file. The only visible code
are the echoes which are the commands themselves. 


Features
--------
◘ Everything run as one program(the modules) instead of like multiple ones thus the entire proccess of steam 
  runs faster because of that.(it's like instead having 20 chrome processes for each tab you have only 1 )

◘ Improves the overlay performance by rendering all the modules(friends panel, community hub....)
  at once instead of each other. [ Tested with PUBG ]

