Run OverlayPerformanceTweak.bat once, all intructions will be onscreen the whole time.
If you ever replace/delete Metro for Steam it will remove the modifications.

Just run OverlayPerformanceTweak.bat if you reinstall the theme.

Features
--------
◘ Improves the overlay performance by rendering all the modules(friends panel, community hub....)
  at once instead of each other. [ Tested with PUBG ]

◘ This will apply to every skin folder that contains metro in name